jimrogers-investments.blogspot.com 2017-06-25

# Jim Rogers Blog.: 01.2008

Privacy Policy  
The blog publisher values the privacy of its clients and Web/blog site viewers. The personal information that may be made available to the blog publisher when browsing or navigating the site shall be kept confidential.  
The blog publisher provides you the opportunity to agree or decline to give your personal information via the Internet. The blog publisher will inform you of the purpose for the collection and does not intend to transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent.

Domain Information Collection  
The blog publisher may collect domain information to enable us to analyze how our visitors use this site. This data enables us to become more familiar with which people visit our site, how often they visit, and what parts of the site they visit most often. The blog publisher uses this information to improve its Web-based offerings. This information is collected automatically and requires no action on your part.

Contextual Advertising on this Blog  
The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.

\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
\- Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to this site users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
The blog publisher reserves the right to change, modify or update this policy at any time without notice. Any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information will be posted on this site.
